{
    "id": "5e8d6f5634b04148b3576f891c847494",
    "title": "Simple Past Or Present Perfect",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ………………… in this city when I was a child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lived",
                "have lived"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a14b201dd6a445d6b18faf3ac24a1d44"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody ………………….. him since yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "has seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "388f5c51cf484716983ef13ec3ada91e"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Where is John?’ ‘He ………………… here ten minutes ago.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b54503f476904f3e9d1d7cd184eb2753"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "died",
                "has died"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c456b117b4954a2aad205830faa29b5c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. since she left school.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was unemployed",
                "has been unemployed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c0876619cea34f4ca627ef1eec817ffb"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ………………….. the contract last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "signed",
                "have signed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "67729318295846b396aa49b347b77be2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The film …………………… . yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has not been released",
                "was not released"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5c5fbfe6581b481b839ffe1742308e44"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………. ill since she returned from Malaysia.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has been",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7af6a94883b94bfdab773fe5df5a6253"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. your brother yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "have met"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a6611041b4eb48ab9f9f33dd44c6aca7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Look. Somebody ………………….. their umbrella behind.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "has left"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fb90b2972389451098593e88a85380b3"
        }
    ]
}